hawkresponder.com 2013-07-15

# HawkResponder Internet Email Advertising Service

PRIVACY POLICY Our Commitment To Privacy 

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage. 

The Information We Collect: This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the HawkResponder website. On some pages, you can order advertising services, make requests, and register to send email advertising or other types of internet advertising. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: Name, Email address and IP address. We do not share, sell or rent this information to outside parties. No other member has access to your email address but can email to your email address through our database. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

Our Commitment To Data Security 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

Our Commitment To Children's Privacy: 

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18. 

How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information 

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging into your account. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by editing your account. 

How To Contact Us: Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at webmaster@hawkresponder.com.
